你觉得人们会注意到你是不是很害羞？
Are you shy? Does this embarrass you? Are you thinking that people will notice your
在开始的时候，你可能会觉得
new accent and criticize you for it? In the beginning, you may feel a little
使用这些新声音时，你一开始可能会觉得奇怪；别担心，它就像一双新鞋。
strange with these new sounds that you're using, but don't worry, it's like a new
一双鞋子，它们需要一段时间才能穿进，让人舒适。
pair of shoes. They take a while to break in and make comfortable. Nevertheless, I
希望你喜欢这个节目。采用一个新的口音也可以成为
hope that you're enjoying this program. Adopting a new accent can become too
这是一个个人化、情绪负担很重的问题，所以不要太严肃。
personal and too emotional an issue, so don't take it too seriously. Relax. Have a
享受这个过程。玩一玩你正在发出的声音。每当一个词或短语
good time. Play with the sounds that you're making. Whenever a word or phrase
你想去一个私人，舒适的地方，试一对。
strikes your fancy, go somewhere private and comfortable and try out a couple
你会像接下来要做的那样，尝试不同的方法、风格和态度，
different approaches, styles, and attitudes with it, as you're going to do
下一个练习中。如果可以，把自己的声音录下来，这样你就能决定哪一种
in the next exercise. If possible, record yourself on tape so you can decide which
一个最适合你。
one suits you best.